Ah, welcome home!
So it really wasn't a dream...
Master! Master!
Today we should do
your master registration!
- Just stick your finger in my va—
- Not right now!
First, we need to get you some
proper clothes and underwear.
I may not be wearing underwear,
but I am wearing clothes.
Yeah, but you look like a cosplayer!
But with that said...
I don't have anything for you to wear.
Well, it's still early.
so I'm going to hit the convenience store.
You're heading out?
- I'll go with you!
- Absolutely not!
You can't just go out commando!
But... l've been here by
myself since I got here.
I'm so... lonely.
Are you tired, master?
Don't call me master when we're out.
What a gust of wind!
It's quite windy today, isn't it?
Are you okay, master?
No I'm not okay!
Come on, the convenience
store's right there!
Ah, okay!
Thanks for coming!
Okay, we've bought them.
Let's get those panties
on her and head home.
Blocked!
Like I said! Making eye contact is
a not signal to kiss me!
I understand.
Okay, here's good.
Go get changed in there.
Sure! I'll be right back.
I'm assuming she at least
knows her way around a restroom.
Why is she still in there?!
Hey! You all right?
Master!
Please, come on in.
Master...
BEWARE OF
PERVERTS!
Let's do your master registration here.
Huh?
Unless you do it, I cannot move.
Huh? What do you—
Master...
All right!
But first, put on those underpants!
Please put them on me, master.
Huh?!
Right, well...
start by lifting your right leg.
I...
I want to be able to serve you
as soon as possible, master.
There are functions I
cannot currently access.
I cannot satisfy you in this state, master!
Make me...
Make me yours and yours alone.
- Excuse meeeee!
- Oh!
Sorry! I'll be right out!
Brought to you by [ToonsHub]
I nearly got caught up in
the heat of the moment..
I am really looking forward to have you take
off the underwear you got for me, master!
I'm going on ahead!
Master!
Still...
Having someone else around...
isn't all that bad.
Master, what did you just—
I-It was nothing! Just forget it!
Why are you so fast?!